<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Campus</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="transfer">Transfer</string>
    <string name="glow">Glow</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="we_have_received_your_payment">We have received your payment.</string>
    <string name="an_initiative_by_satyansh_rai">An initiative by Satyansh Rai</string>
    <string name="about_us"><![CDATA[Smart campus is an initiative to bring about a  digitalization revolution in BITS Pilani, Pilani campus. \n\nWhat do we aim to achieve? \n\nWe target smart facilities for the students at BITS Pilani, in line with the standards maintained by the highest ranked universities across the globe. \n\nHow do we plan on bringing about this change ? \n\nIn the system\'s initial phase, we can order food online, from any location on campus.No need to waste your time in queues… ever again. This system also does away with the unnecessary hassle of carrying your ID card around campus all the time.Upcoming features include extending similar facilities at ANC, and more importantly - S9. All you need to do is simply upload  the documents -that you want printed - to the Smart Campus app and the printouts would be ready at S9 by the time you arrived.How convenient, right ? This feature will soon follow the existing ones. \n\nPROCEDURE :- \n\n1) Order items on the app \n2) Order received by FK/looters \n3) Notification sent to the user when its preparation starts \n4) Order Ready \n5) Notification sent to the user \n6) Collect it without wasting any time waiting in a queue. \n\nBILL SPLIT :- \n\nWe have added a feature to facilitate the splitting of bills between people. \n\nSuppose you wish to share a pizza ( let\'s say it costs Rs 200 )with your friend. Your friend can order the pizza through his app, and you can just pay him Rs 100 , via the \' *money transfer* \' feature provided. Finally, both you and your friend will be charged Rs. 100 from your respective SWD accounts. \n\nSimple right ? \nGreat ! \n\nLet\'s order. What do you wanna have ?]]></string>
</resources>
